modasta.com 2018-06-30

# PRIVACY POLICY - Modasta

**Effective from April, 2016**

MODASTA (A Tasman Drive Software Private Ltd venture) is a Digital Healthcare Platform:  
Modasta (“We” and/or “Us” and/or “Company”) is concerned about the privacy of its users (“User(s)” and/or “You” and/or “Your”) accessing its online platform in the name and style of modasta.com

Please read the Privacy Policy (“Policy”) carefully before using the Website/Application, along with the Terms of Use (“ToU”) provided on the Website/Application. Your use of the Website/ Application or the services provided by the Website/Application shall signify Your acceptance of this Policy and Your agreement to be legally bound by the same.

If You do not agree with the terms of this Policy, do not use the Website/ Application or avail any of the services offered on this Website/Application.

**1\. ABOUT THE POLICY:**

When You register with the Website/ Application, We may seek and collect certain personal information for your use of the Website/ Application. You consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of the information in accordance with this Policy. Therefore, We request You to read this carefully before using the Website/ Application.  
Please note that, We respect and value Your privacy and shall strive towards protecting the information that You provide. We shall keep the information provided to Us as confidential to the extent reasonably possible. The prior permission of every User is sought before any personal information is collected. If at any time You wish to have Your information deleted, you can write to Us on privacy@modasta.com. We shall do the needful within 7 working days.

**2\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION AND ITS USE:**

For the purposes of this Policy, such information that can be uniquely identified to You shall be known as the personal information.

The personal information You may provide to Us that We may use is as follows:

1\. Registration details: This will include the password provided by You for which we use reasonable security measures for password protection from anyone.  
2\. Your usage behavior on the Website/ Application.  
3\. The medical information that you may post/provide on the Website/ Application.  
4\. The details of the computer system or computer network that You use to visit the Website/Application and any activities undertaken through the usage of this system.

The fundamental reason behind collecting Your personal information is to support and facilitate You to enjoy various features and services provided by the Website/ Application.

We select and track Your preferences to provide You with a customized Website/ Application experience, to notify You of any updated information and new developments/features and other related functions offered by the Website/ Application, to otherwise support Your relationship with Us or to prevent fraud and unlawful use.

By accepting the terms of this Policy, You understand, agree and recognize that our storage and processing of Your personal information is for a lawful purpose associated with a function or an activity of the Website/ Application. You further understand, agree and acknowledge that You may be required to provide personal information that is classified as sensitive personal information as per applicable laws for Us to provide various services to You and for Your usage of the Website/Application and other services provided by the Website/ Application.

Please note that, it is entirely upto the discretion of the User to provide this personal information.

We do not sell, trade or rent Your personal information to any third party unless We have been expressly authorized by You either in writing or electronically to do so. We may at times provide aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third parties, however this information when disclosed will be in an aggregate form and does not contain any of Your personally identifiable information.

We may disclose Your personal information solely in the legitimate conduct of the business to deliver services to meet Your demands. We may also release information when We believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (1) comply with legal or regulatory requirements; (2) enforce or apply terms of the our Website/Application user agreement; or (3) protect our rights, property or safety of the rights of others.  
You may note that, We adopt reasonable security measures to protect Your password from being exposed or disclosed to anyone.

**3\. INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE:  **  
We are the recipient of all the personal information and shall exercise reasonable care to keep Your personal information confidential to the maximum possible extent. We may limit disclosure of the Users’ information to our entities, joint ventures, agents, contractors, participating doctors or third parties for the purposes of the services provided by them or for any other marketing related activity undertaken by or on behalf of the our entities and/or its joint ventures on a need-to-know basis. We will ensure on reasonable commercial efforts basis that the doctors participating on the Website/ Application are under an obligation to maintain confidentiality with respect to the personal information provided by the Users during the course of obtaining online consultations or otherwise and to use it strictly for the purposes of the providing the services as required by the Users and as contemplated by Us. However, We shall not be liable for any unauthorized use or disclosure of the personal information by such participating doctors or any other entity to whom such information may be disclosed.

All payments for the services availed on the Website/Application shall be made on the secured payment gateway. We shall use necessary measures to protect the payment gateway from any unauthorized use however, We shall not be responsible for any such use which is beyond the reasonable control of the Website/Application.

**4\. LEGAL COMPLIANCE:**  
We abide by all the applicable laws in force as well as the mandates of government agencies. We will disclose any information about You to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as We, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal processes, to protect the property and rights of the Company or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally fraudulent activity. We may also provide Your Personal Information to various regulatory authorities upon any demand or request from them.

**5\. BUSINESS TRANSFERS:**

We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

**6\. EMAIL POLICIES:**

You can choose the type of emails that You wish to receive from Us. If You decide at any time that You no longer wish to receive such communications from Us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. Please note that once We receive Your request, it may take an additional period of time for Your subscription to become ineffective.

**7\. DELETING YOUR INFORMATION:  **  
If You wish to have the Personal Information that You have provided to us deleted, You can do so by writing to Us on privacy@modasta.com. Please note that deletion of certain Personal Information may lead to deletion of Your account with the Website/Application and Your access to certain features of the Website/ Application.

**8\. SECURITY:   **  
We strive to work towards the security, integrity and privacy of Your personal information and to protect Your personal Information against unauthorized disclosure, access or destruction to the extent reasonably possible by Us. Notwithstanding anything contained in this Policy or elsewhere, the We shall not be held responsible for any loss, damage or misuse of Your Personal Information, if such loss, damage or misuse takes place as a result of a Force Majeure Event (as defined below).

A “Force Majeure Event” shall mean any event that is beyond our reasonable control and shall include, without limitation, fire, flood, explosion, acts of God, civil commotion, strikes, insurrection, war, acts of government, computer hacking, software failure and storage device, computer crashes etc.

**9\. LINKS TO OTHER SITES:**

The Website/ Application provides third-party advertisements and links to other websites. We do not provide Your personal information to these third-party websites or advertisers.  
The links to other websites are operated by third parties and are not controlled by, or affiliated to, or associated with Us unless expressly specified on the Website/ Application. Therefore, We do not make any claims concerning the privacy practices or policies of such third parties or terms of use of such websites, nor do We control or guarantee or endorse the accuracy, integrity, or quality of the information available on such websites. Any information provided by You to such third party websites shall be governed in accordance with the privacy policies of the respective websites and it is strongly recommended that You review the privacy policy on any such websites prior to using such websites.

**10\. CHANGES IN PRIVACY POLICY:**

We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time, so please visit the Website/ Application regularly to review our privacy statement.

**11\. PHISHING:**

Identity theft and the fraudulent practice currently known as “phishing” are of great concern to Us. Phishing is an attempt to acquire personal/sensitive information which the legitimate organization already has. Safeguarding information to help protect You from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request Your credit card information or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

**12\. COOKIES:**

We may also collect certain non-personal information through cookies while You access the Website/ Application. Cookies are text files that are placed in Your computer to identify Your internet browser, store Your preferences, and to improve Your experience on the Website/Application.  
We use cookies in order to improve our services provided to You. Please note that some cookies we use are essential for some services to work, others are used to collect information of the use of the Website/ Application so that the Website/ Application can be more convenient and useful for You.

**13\. CONTACT US:**

If You have any questions about this Policy, the practices of the Company or your dealings with the Website/ Application, You can contact Us via email on privacy@modasta.com.  
Copyright Modasta © All rights reserved.
